<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Madison Mansouri</title>
    <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Madison Mansouri</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://54.147.1.162:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Callaway</title>
      <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/callaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/callaway/</guid>
      <description>by Emily Pope&#xA;University of Tennessee, Knoxville Location: Knoxville, TN - 2024&#xA;Roles &amp;amp; Team:&#xA;Director: Madison M. Mansouri Stage Manager: Cameron Skillen Scenic Design: Jamie Jaymes &amp;amp; Kevin Collins Costumes: Patti Rogers Sound Design: Jamie Jaymes Painting: Reilly Chisholm Synopsis An emotionally stirring world premiere that explores the intertwining lives of a small community, uncovering hidden truths, confronting fears, and embracing redemption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midsummer Night&#39;s Dream</title>
      <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/midsummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/midsummer/</guid>
      <description>Knoxville Shakespeare Location: Knoxville, TN - 2024&#xA;Roles &amp;amp; Team:&#xA;Co-Director: LB Wells Choreographer: Madison M. Mansouri Stage Manager: Cameron Skillen Music Director: Chip Morris Scenic Design: Jamie Jaymes &amp;amp; Kevin Collins Costumes: Patti Rogers Sound Design: Jamie Jaymes Painting: Reilly Chisholm Props: Lillian Wells Synopsis Four mismatched lovers woo, a group of aspiring thespians rehearse a play, and the rulers of the fairy kingdom have a royal rumble—all within the same woods on the same night—with hilarious results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Romeo &amp; Juliet</title>
      <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/randj/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/randj/</guid>
      <description>Knoxville Shakespeare Location: Knoxville, TN - 2024&#xA;Roles &amp;amp; Team:&#xA;Co-Director: H. Caitlin Corbitt Fight Director: Gray Casterline Music Director: Chip Morris Stage Manager: Marcos Gonzalez Dramaturgy: Laura Snyder Scenic Design: Jamie Jaymes &amp;amp; Kevin Collins Costumes: Patti Rogers Sound Design: Jamie Jaymes Painting: Reilly Chisholm Synopsis Two star-crossed lovers shine brightly, only to have their love extinguished as soon as it ignites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming of the Shrew</title>
      <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/shrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/shrew/</guid>
      <description>Knoxville Shakespeare Location: Knoxville, TN - 2024&#xA;Roles &amp;amp; Team:&#xA;Co-Directors: Madison M. Mansouri &amp;amp; LB Wells Choreographer: Madison M. Mansouri Stage Manager: Cameron Skillen Music Director: Chip Morris Scenic Design: Jamie Jaymes &amp;amp; Kevin Collins Costumes: Patti Rogers Sound Design: Jamie Jaymes Painting: Reilly Chisholm Props: Lillian Wells Synopsis A battle of wits, humor, and romance unfolds in Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s bold comedy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Wolves</title>
      <link>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/wolves/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>http://54.147.1.162:1313/portfolio/wolves/</guid>
      <description>by Sarah DeLappe&#xA;University of Tennessee, Knoxville Location: Knoxville, TN - 2024&#xA;Roles &amp;amp; Team:&#xA;Director: Madison M. Mansouri Stage Manager: Cameron Skillen Scenic Design: Jamie Jaymes &amp;amp; Kevin Collins Costumes: Patti Rogers Sound Design: Jamie Jaymes Painting: Reilly Chisholm Synopsis An intimate and raw portrayal of a girls&amp;rsquo; indoor soccer team as they navigate the challenges of adolescence, competition, and camaraderie.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
